WHEN HACKERS COULDN'T
TRICK THEIR VICTIMS
INTO HANDING OVER
THEIR CRYPTO
THEY CALLED
MARLON FERRO
HE'D BREAK INTO
YOUR HOUSE
AND TAKE IT
FERRO, 20, WAS
THE "INSTRUMENT
OF LAST RESORT"
FOR A
$250 MILLION
SOCIAL-ENGINEERING RING
WHEN VICTIMS STORED
THEIR CRYPTO ON
HARDWARE WALLETS —
DEVICES THAT
CAN'T BE HACKED
REMOTELY —
THE ENTERPRISE
SENT HIM IN
FEBRUARY 2024
WINNSBORO, TEXAS
FERRO BROKE INTO
A HOME
AND WALKED OUT WITH
100 BITCOIN
MORE THAN
FIVE MILLION DOLLARS
JULY 2024
NEW MEXICO
HE STAKED OUT
THE HOUSE FOR DAYS
WHEN CO-CONSPIRATORS
TRACKED THE VICTIM'S iCLOUD
AND CONFIRMED
HE WAS GONE
FERRO SMASHED
A WINDOW WITH A BRICK
THE HOME CAMERA
CAUGHT HIM
THE STOLEN MONEY
BOUGHT HERMÈS
BIRKIN BAGS
EXOTIC CARS
UP TO $3.8 MILLION
NIGHTCLUB TABS OF
HALF A MILLION A NIGHT
AND PRIVATE JETS
FERRO WAS ARRESTED
WITH TWO FIREARMS
AND A FAKE ID
THIS MONTH
A FEDERAL JUDGE
SENTENCED HIM TO
78 MONTHS IN PRISON —
AND $2.5 MILLION
IN RESTITUTION